



PERSONAL INFO

phone

+36 20 388 8827

email

hello@tengerbori.hu

website

http://www.tengerbori.hu

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/boritenger/

Behance

https://www.behance.net/borimoon

TECHNICAL SKILLS

visual design

prototyping

front-end design

SOFT SKILLS

collaboration

user empathy

client relations

communication

self-motivation

BIO

I'm a designer who excels in all aspects of UI design. I have many years of history creating visuals for both physical and online products.

Currently, I'm focusing on creating user interfaces. I natively speak HTML, CSS, and also gained some valuable knowledge of JavaScript. My skills and learnings allow me to bring ideas from concept to prototypes and then to production.

EXPERIENCE

UI Designer

OPPI | Oct 2017 - present

Currently, I collaborate with a freelance team named Oppi. I work on digital projects from smart hotel user interfaces to website design and development.

Designer

WINKLER & STENZEL | Oct 2011 - Apr 2018

I worked on both print and digital products. I participated in several advertising campaigns, branding, and rebranding projects. I designed and developed websites and product landing pages for our clients.

Graphic Designer

ART-VERSIO ADVERTISING AGENCY | Mar 2010 - Oct 2011

Lecturer

ÓBUDA UNIVERSITY REJTŐ SÁNDOR FACULTY | Sep 2009 - Dec 2009

EDUCATION

Front-end Development

MOME CODE | 2015

Bachelor's Degree Print and Multimedia

ÓBUDA UNIVERSITY REJTŐ SÁNDOR FACULTY | 2009

Graphic Design

ART SCHOOL OF BUDA | 2004